# **BRAVARD** Amadis

amadis.bravard[AT]outlook.com - I https://www.amadisbravard.fr/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dix/ - 🔘 https://www.github.com/dix/ French/English - 💓 Lille, France

# Technical Lead/Solution Architect

For more than ten years, first as a Full-Stack Software Engineer then as a Technical Lead, I was able to learn about various functional domains (healthcare, banking/insurance...) while working with multiple technologies (Java, Angular, Node.js, Unix, Cloud...).

Now, after collecting and analyzing the requirements, I design interoperability solutions that best meet the expectations of customers/users while staying within the constraints of each stakeholder.

If it isn't documented, it doesn't exist

# Professional Experience

## 2019-01 to Present: Dedalus (ex-Inovelan) - Healthcare

### **Technical Lead then Solution Architect**

- Collecting and analyzing the requirements
- Designing solutions with the international partners and tracking their implementation
- Implementing development industrialization practices (Jira, documentation, code review...)
- Organizing brainstorms and continuous improvement practice workshops (process, POC, English...)
- Participating in presales, technical and functional designing workshops
- Conducting technical interviews

#### **Environment**

- J2EE, Angular, Node.js, REST, Git, HL7 FHIR, Drone Cl, Docker, Unix, Agile (Scrum)
- 5 to 20 people

# 2010-11 to 2018-12: Inetum (ex-GFI Informatique) - IT Services

## Intern, Technical Analyst then Technical Lead

- Training and monitoring the team members
- Estimating, designing and developing features/fixesQuality control : PCI DSS/OWASP Top 10
- Managing development/testing environments
- Writing technical and functional documentation
- Backup project manager
- Conducting technical interviews

#### **Customers - Domains**

- Pacifica (Crédit Agricole) Insurance
- Payline (Monext) Web payment
- Metro Cash&Carry Retail
- France Télécom (Órange) Automation

## **Environment**

- J2EE, Angular, Bash, SVN, Git, Unix, Agile (Scrum)
- 5 to 20 people

# Education/Training

#### **Professionals**

2016-12 : Développement d'applications riches avec Angular 2 - Zénika

2016-05 : AngularJS, maîtriser le Framework JavaScript de Google – Orsys

2015-04 : OWASP, Sécurité des Applications - Advens

2009-01 to 2011-01 : D.U.T. Informatique - IUT A Lille 1

# (=) Interests

Cycling (utility, road, virtual & MTB)

Personal Knowledge Management

Soap-making